{
    "subject": "resource/Lotte_Stam-Beese",
    "predicate": "http://www.w3.org/2000/01/rdf-schema#comment",
    "object": "Charlotte Ida Anna \"Lotte\" Stam-Beese (nee Beese, January 28, 1903 - November 18, 1988) was a German architect and urban planner who helped with the reconstruction of Rotterdam after World War II.",
    "human_readable": "The comment about Lotte Stam-Beese is Charlotte Ida Anna 'Lotte' Stam-Beese (nee Beese, January 28, 1903 - November 18, 1988) was a German architect and urban planner who helped with the reconstruction of Rotterdam after World War II.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8395983576774597,
            "question": "Which city did Lotte Stam-Beese help rebuild after a major conflict?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.755340039730072,
            "question": "What was Lotte Stam-Beese's profession?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7459526658058167,
            "question": "When was Lotte Stam-Beese born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7459467053413391,
            "question": "What role did Lotte Stam-Beese play in post-war reconstruction?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7345672845840454,
            "question": "What was Lotte Stam-Beese's maiden name?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.724412202835083,
            "question": "In what century was Lotte Stam-Beese born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7078441977500916,
            "question": "What country was Lotte Stam-Beese from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6430599689483643,
            "question": "What type of projects did Lotte Stam-Beese work on?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6379007697105408,
            "question": "When did Lotte Stam-Beese die?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6135439276695251,
            "question": "What significant event occurred during Lotte Stam-Beese's lifetime?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The comment about Lotte Stam-Beese is Charlotte Ida Anna 'Lotte' Stam-Beese (nee Beese, January 28, 1903 - November 18, 1988) was a German architect and urban planner who helped with the reconstruction of Rotterdam after World War II.",
            "html": "dbpedia_1563_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=When did Lotte Stam-Beese die?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1563_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What type of projects did Lotte Stam-Beese work on?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1563_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What country was Lotte Stam-Beese from?",
            "html": "dbpedia_1563_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1563_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1563_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1563_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1563_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1563_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1563_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1563_68.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1563_77.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1563_79.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_1563_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you have any other triples you'd like me to evaluate!  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the answer in the structured JSON format:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```\n\nThe provided context information supports the statement about Lotte Stam-Beese being an architect and urban planner who contributed to the reconstruction of Rotterdam post-World War II."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}